<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts | Harospec</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Posts</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/post/CopyOffeatured.jpg</url>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backcountry Ski Tours</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;Information about snowpack and weather conditions is important for safe and enjoyable experiences skiing in the backcountry. I track my ski tours using GAIA GPS and record information on each tour, such as elevation gain, weather, and other observations. This rmarkdown webapp displays some of the backcountry ski tours I’ve taken over the last few years.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Funding</title>
      <link>/post/funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/funding/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;PSRC’s 2016 FHWA/FTA Project Selection Process distributed $200 million in federal transportation dollars to transportation projects around the Puget Sound region. I provided support to this process by helping to build the selection criteria and subsequently comparing each project and weighing the benefits of each against criteria to develop comparable scores. In additional, I developed data visualizations that displayed the funds awarded to the winning projects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://public.tableau.com/profile/reid5830#!/vizhome/project_selection_RH/Story1&#34; width=&#34;950px&#34; height=&#34;800px&#34;&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ornithology</title>
      <link>/post/bird/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/bird/</guid>
      <description>


&lt;p&gt;Using the eBird app, I record observations of the birds I identify while traveling and around my home. I created a workflow for obtaining and wrangling my eBird database with ‘google sheets’ and ‘dplyr’, as well as a visualization of my bird observations using ‘Rmarkdown’ with additional usage of ‘leaflet’ and ‘datatable’. The result is a quick and easy way to track and understand the various birds that I have observed over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://rhaefer.github.io/bird.html&#34; width=&#34;950px&#34; height=&#34;800px&#34;&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
